ptd.net 2018-02-04

# Privacy Policy | PTD

PenTeleData LP 1. is the organization that produces the PenTeleData Website (Website). We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Website.

**General  **  
You may visit our website without disclosing any personal information. We may, however, offer some services or specifically request personal information. The personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to, first and last name, street address, email address, telephone number (e.g., home, work, mobile and/or fax), and birthdate. We may also collect other personal information that will be identified on the applicable page(s) of the Website. If you submit any personal information to us, or to our third party service providers acting on our behalf, you can be assured that we will not sell, lease, or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as follows: (1) to our third party service providers, and only so that they may help us provide the services you've requested and in certain circumstances to provide you with ticket or merchandise related offers; and (2) on occasion, we may offer a special promotion (such as a sweepstakes or other contests on the Website or otherwise or in conjunction with a third party service provider, sponsor or promotional partner, and share your information with that sponsor or promotional partner so that it can send you other special promotions it offers, but only if you give us permission to do so.

**Special Offers and Promotions  **

With your permission, we may also send you emails with special offers and promotions. If you don't want to receive these, you may unsubscribe to our newsletter.

**Automatically Collected Information**    
We may use automatic methods such as cookies (small amounts of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive) to understand Website trends, deliver a more personalized experience and to improve our content and offerings. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze using these methods include, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; email address; type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we may aggregate with similar information from other customers; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, on, and from our Website, including date and time; and cookie information. We may also use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to accept or reject cookies. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain services on our Website.

We do not transfer cookies associated with our Website to any unrelated company, nor do we authorize any other companies to access the cookies we have placed on your computer's hard drive. We may allow other companies that are presenting advertisements or providing services on our pages to set and access cookies on your computer. Those companies' use of cookies will be covered by their own privacy policies, not ours.

We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with our Website, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. "Spyware" or "adware" is any software which has been downloaded to and/or installed on an Internet user's computer, without the user's actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred.

**Aggregated Demographic Information  **  
We may share aggregated demographic information with third parties, but this information is not linked to any personal information that can identify you or another individual person. Therefore, no personal information is disclosed in this manner. Business Transfers. In the future, PenTeleData LP 1 may be sold along with its assets, or other transactions may occur in which customer information is one of the business assets transferred. In such a case, the customer information which we have gathered may be one of the business assets we transfer. Disclosure for Legal Purposes. The law requires that we may be required to share your personal information and non-personal information (see "Cookies" section above for examples of non-personal information) pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use and disclose share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Website's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Links**    
Our Website contains links to other sites websites operated by unrelated third parties. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when your leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of every website that collects personally identifiable information from you. The Privacy Policy applies only to this Website.

**Contact Us  **  
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us.

**Notification of Changes**    
Any changes to this policy will be listed on this page.

LAST UPDATED AND EFFECTIVE DATE: DEC 11, 2013.
